http://www.reddingmedical.com/privacy

Log In
Redding Medical has been a trusted medical equipment provider for healthcare professionals since 1975.
Redding Medical Inc. - Medical Equipment and Scrubs
Cart:
(0 item)
- $0.00
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Subtotal: $0.00
Search:
Stethoscopes
Littmann StethoscopesLittmann Stethoscope Selection3M™ Littmann® Electronic Stethoscope3M™ Littmann® Cardiology Series3M™ Littmann® Classic Series 3M™ Littmann® Lightweight3M™ Littmann® Pediatric & Infant Single-Patient StethoscopesParts & AccessoriesEngrave Existing StethoscopeSpecial Finishes Veterinary Teaching Discount DemosMismarkedEko StethoscopesStudent KitsNursing KitsMedical StudentsWelch Allyn StethoscopesStethoscope PartsADC Electronic StethoscopesCardionicsUltraScope Stethoscope AccessoriesMDF
Diagnostic Sets
Welch Allyn Diagnostic SetsNi-Cad Oto / Ophthalmoscope SetsLithium-Ion Oto / Ophthalmoscope SetsPanOptic SetsPocket SetsDesk SetsADC Diagnostic Sets
Diagnostics
Blood PressureDigitalStandardWall/DeskThermometrySureTempBraun PartsHome UsePulse OximetersFingertip Pulse OximetersWelch AllynPatient MonitorsConnex® SpotConnex® VitalSpot LXiSpot VitalWall Transformers GS 777 767 SeriesConnexLightingWelch Allyn Exam LightsDiagnostic HeadlightsWelch Allyn's EpiScope Skin Surface MicroscopeEENTTympanometersAudiometersVision ScreenerRetinoscopesEar WashLaryngoscopeDopplersHand-HeldABI/VascularTable TopAccessoriesCardiopulmonaryAmbulatory Blood Pressure MonitorCardioPerfect WorkstationDefibrillatorsWelch Allyn Home™ HypertensionWomen's HealthVaginal SpeculaSigmoidoscopes / ColposcopesSpecula Lighting SystemEndoscopyWelch Allyn Endoscopic Illumination SystemsWelch Allyn Endoscopic PartsEKGSpiro
Scrubs
CherokeeStatementHeartSoulCode HappyInfinityRunway by CherokeeTopsPrint TopsPantsWorkwearFlexiblesCherokee Luxe Cherokee Disney CollectionCherokee TooniformsMen'sWarm-Up JacketsVera Bradley Scrubs Skechers ScrubsFour-Stretch Pet Friendly Scrubs by WinkBarco EdgeBarco MotionBarco One Scrubs by Barco UniformsDickiesEDS ScrubsGeneration FlexExtreme StretchMen's/Unisex ScrubsLab CoatsPantsPrintsSolid TopsGrey's Anatomy Scrubs by Barco UniformsGrey's AnatomyGrey's SignatureMen's ScrubsShoesHealing Hands ScrubsMedcoutureCarharttWonderWinkAEROW123 - by WonderWinkWonderWORKLab CoatsLadiesMen's/Unisex Lab CoatsMen's ScrubsTopsPantsWarm-Up JacketsT-Shirts and Polo ShirtsBreast CancerDressesMaternityPrintsScrub Hats/CapsICU Scrubs By BarcoChefWearLandauTopsPantsMen's ScrubsLab CoatsSeasonalFall ScrubsChristmas ScrubsValentines
FOOTWEAR
ShoesSocks & Hosiery
Parts
Littmann Parts & AccessoriesWelch Allyn PartsStethoscope PartsBatteriesBlood Pressure Bulbs/ LampsEarTipsPower HandlesOphthalmoscope HeadsOtoscope HeadsVaginal SpeculaSpeculaPulse Oximetry PartsThermometer PartsMobile Stand or Wall  MountCasesMiscellaneous
Instruments
ForcepsScissorsNeurologic HammersTuning ForksPensPenlightsDissecting KitsMeasuring ToolsInstrument Kits
Gifts Under $10.00
Gifts Under $20.00
Miscellaneous
BagsClipboardsCPR MasksThermometersGifts Under $10.00Gifts Under $50.00Gifts Under $100.00Gift IdeasBreast Cancer ProductsEmblem PinsEMT SuppliesEye ChartsEyewear / GogglesGift CardsID HoldersOrganizersPediaPal ProductsWatchesSkeletonsName BadgesMiscellaneousClearanceScrubs  & ShoesMedical EquipmentStethoscopesMiscellaneousGloves, & Disposables
Scales
Seca Upright / Physician ScalesSeca PediatricSeca Floor ScalesSeca Multifunction and Wheelchair ScalesSeca Digital Personal ScalesMeasuring DevicesSeca Bed and Dialysis ScalesSeca Chair ScalesSeca Carrying CasesSeca Accessories
Schools
Home
/
Privacy Policy
Redding Medical Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how Redding Medical uses and protects any information that you give Redding Medical when you use this website.
Redding Medical is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
Redding Medical may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time.
What we collect:
We may collect the following information:
name and job titlecontact information including email addressdemographic information such as postcode, preferences and interestsother information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
What we do with the information we gather:
We use your personal information to provide you products and services, such as to fulfill your requests for products or to help us personalize our offerings to you. We also use your personal information to support our business functions, such as fraud prevention, marketing, and legal functions. and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping:We may use the information to improve our products and services.We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
Security:We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies:A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites:Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
..
Copyright © 2013 Redding Medical™ Equipment all rights reserved.
Trusted medical supplies for healthcare professionals since 1975.
